{"data":[{"question":"Has the advertising agency ___ the new promotional material yet? I need it by this afternoon.\n","a":"dropped off","b":"dropped in","c":"dropped out","d":"dropped by","answer":"1","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"57","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"We need to ________ the price of the product, which is relatively high, and focus on its quality as a selling point.\n","a":"back down","b":"break down","c":"play down","d":"settle down ","answer":"3","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"57","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"Have you ___ any other interesting product features that we could emphasize in the ads?\n","a":"come across","b":"drawn out","c":"gotten across","d":"made out","answer":"1","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"57","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"We've decided to ___ billboards and use more double-page spreads instead.\n","a":"back off on","b":"come down with","c":"cut back on","d":"drop off","answer":"3","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"57","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"This poster is horrible and can't be used. The colors and images are all wrong. We will have to ___ .\n","a":"do it over","b":"even it out","c":"do it in","d":"put it down","answer":"1","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"57","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"We had to reorder the printed advertisements because the printer completely forgot and ___ the free sample coupons.\n","a":"kept off","b":"left out","c":"passed out","d":"shaved off","answer":"2","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"57","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"We're going to have to ___ the advertising campaign if we can't get any TV or radio time.\n","a":"call on","b":"call off","c":"drop off","d":"drop out","answer":"2","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"57","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"This commercial doesn't seem to promote the product. Can you explain to me how dancing chickens ___ sport shoes?\n","a":"pan out as","b":"hold up to","c":"add up to","d":"have to do with","answer":"4","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"57","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"I like that magazine, but I think we should ___ advertising in it until its circulation has increased.\n","a":"put out","b":"put back","c":"put away","d":"put off ","answer":"4","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"57","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"},{"question":"My new assistant needs to be ___ before I trust her to run an ad campaign like this one. \n","a":"broken down","b":"broken in","c":"broken up","d":"broken into","answer":"2","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"57","subcategorylv2":"7","type":"1"}]}